{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "I ________ in the forest.",
      "a": "am",
      "b": "is",
      "c": "are",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "Affirmative: I + am.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mrs Hill's daughter ________ clever.",
      "a": "am not",
      "b": "isn't",
      "c": "aren't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "Negative: he/she/it + isn't/is not.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sasha and Valera ________ friends.",
      "a": "am",
      "b": "is",
      "c": "are",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "Affirmative: you/we/they + are.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mrs.Green's aunt ________ a doctor.",
      "a": "am not",
      "b": "isn't",
      "c": "aren't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "Negative: he/she/it + isn't/is not.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "The frog ________ funny.",
      "a": "am",
      "b": "is",
      "c": "are",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "The frog (singular) + is ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "The women ________ in the room.",
      "a": "am",
      "b": "is",
      "c": "are",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "The women (plural) + are",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "My name ________ Vera.",
      "a": "am not",
      "b": "isn't",
      "c": "aren't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "My name (singular) + is(not)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "I ________ nine.",
      "a": "am not",
      "b": "isn't",
      "c": "aren't",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "I am not",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "She ________ a teacher.",
      "a": "am not",
      "b": "isn't",
      "c": "aren't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "He/she/it + isn't/is not.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "The bags ________ in the room.",
      "a": "am",
      "b": "is",
      "c": "are",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "The bags (plural) + are ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "8",
      "subcategorylv2": "1",
      "type": "2"
    }
  ]
}